const QUESTIONS_DATA = [[{"qid": "Q1", "type": "select-all", "questionText": "Every morning, Rajeev spends an hour alone drawing a portrait from a photograph in the day\u2019s newspaper to improve his portraiture skills (skills drawing a portrait). Yet, despite a year of practice, his drawing skills do not seem to improved. Why might simply practicing a portrait a day not yield an improvement?", "choices": [{"cid": "c", "text": "Even without deliberate practice, Rajeev could improve his skill by practice. If his skill doesn't improve at all, that is not a problem of deliberate practice, it's a problem that he didn't practice the same skill every day. He is not practicing a specific skill (draw the eye of the portrait). Although the lack of feedback is also important, it's more important to focus on the same practice)"}, {"cid": "d", "text": "The task of creating a portrait is a complex one and should be studied step by step rather than in full. Hence, Rajeev should identify what parts of the portrait are problematic and practice them regularly instead of drawing new full portrait every day."}, {"cid": "a", "text": "He is not doing deliberate practice. B/c there is no feedback provided."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "Currently, Rajeev is not receiving feedback and remedial instruction for his work which are an integral part of deliberate practice."}], "correctChoices": ["a", "b"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}, {"qid": "Q1", "type": "multiple-choice", "questionText": "Every morning, Rajeev spends an hour alone drawing a portrait from a photograph in the day\u2019s newspaper to improve his portraiture skills (skills drawing a portrait). Yet, despite a year of practice, his drawing skills do not seem to improved. Why might simply practicing a portrait a day not yield an improvement?", "choices": [{"cid": "c", "text": "The task of creating a portrait is a complex one and should be studied step by step rather than in full. Hence, Rajeev should identify what parts of the portrait are problematic and practice them regularly instead of drawing new full portrait every day."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "Even without deliberate practice, Rajeev could improve his skill by practice. If his skill doesn't improve at all, that is not a problem of deliberate practice, it's a problem that he didn't practice the same skill every day. He is not practicing a specific skill (draw the eye of the portrait). Although the lack of feedback is also important, it's more important to focus on the same practice)"}, {"cid": "a", "text": "He is not doing deliberate practice. B/c there is no feedback provided."}, {"cid": "d", "text": "lack of deliberate practice, to say, always practice a general and broad task set without pinpointing where exactly is not good."}], "correctChoice": ["a"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}, {"qid": "Q1", "type": "select-all", "questionText": "Every morning, Rajeev spends an hour alone drawing a portrait from a photograph in the day\u2019s newspaper to improve his portraiture skills (skills drawing a portrait). Yet, despite a year of practice, his drawing skills do not seem to improved. Why might simply practicing a portrait a day not yield an improvement?", "choices": [{"cid": "a", "text": "Reason could be because he didn't get corrective feedback."}, {"cid": "d", "text": "it's not deliberate practice"}, {"cid": "b", "text": "Because he doesn't have a mentor who diagnoses his problems about painting. He doesn't get immediate feedback and remedial training."}, {"cid": "c", "text": "lack of deliberate practice, to say, always practice a general and broad task set without pinpointing where exactly is not good."}], "correctChoices": ["a", "b"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}], [{"qid": "Q2", "type": "multiple-choice", "questionText": "Dan wants to improve his golf game. Every day, he practices one golf stroke for an hour, and records his practice session on video. After his practice, he watches the recording, and plans on what changes to make the next day. Assume he has no other golf instruction. Is Dan engaged in deliberate practice? Why?", "choices": [{"cid": "a", "text": "The feedback needs to be given by an external agent"}, {"cid": "d", "text": "No. Deliberate practice requires feedback from an external expert, be that a human expert or an agent. Also, he is not making adjustments frequent enough"}, {"cid": "c", "text": "No, because deliberate practice requires that an external agent provide feedback to the learner."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "Yes, he has isolated a specific task, practices it repeatedly and reviews his sessions to narrow on improvements."}], "correctChoice": ["a"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}, {"qid": "Q2", "type": "select-all", "questionText": "Dan wants to improve his golf game. Every day, he practices one golf stroke for an hour, and records his practice session on video. After his practice, he watches the recording, and plans on what changes to make the next day. Assume he has no other golf instruction. Is Dan engaged in deliberate practice? Why?", "choices": [{"cid": "d", "text": "No, because deliberate practice requires that an external agent provide feedback to the learner."}, {"cid": "a", "text": "The feedback needs to be given by an external agent"}, {"cid": "c", "text": "Yes, he has isolated a specific task, practices it repeatedly and reviews his sessions to narrow on improvements."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "It is. Because it includes practice on a specific skill, supervised by himself, get feedback from himself, and remedial training the next day."}], "correctChoices": ["a", "b"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}], [{"qid": "Q3", "type": "multiple-choice", "questionText": "Mark is learning to play the guitar. After long hours of practice, he mastered playing his favorite song. Write one growth-mindset building feedback his instructor could give him.", "choices": [{"cid": "a", "text": "Great, you are doing well on this song because of your hard practice. You could do better on other songs and more complex skills if you continue to practice like this."}, {"cid": "d", "text": "Amazing job! Great persistent on your learning."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "One of the most important things about growth mindset is giving feedback on the task that Mark is doing and not on his own personality of him being a talented musician. One growth mindset instruction his instructor could give him is \"Great work in your performance today. Keep up with your perseverance.\""}, {"cid": "c", "text": "You have improved a lot!"}], "correctChoice": ["a"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}, {"qid": "Q3", "type": "select-all", "questionText": "Mark is learning to play the guitar. After long hours of practice, he mastered playing his favorite song. Write one growth-mindset building feedback his instructor could give him.", "choices": [{"cid": "d", "text": "You have improved a lot!"}, {"cid": "b", "text": "Good job on practicing the right skill!"}, {"cid": "c", "text": "One of the most important things about growth mindset is giving feedback on the task that Mark is doing and not on his own personality of him being a talented musician. One growth mindset instruction his instructor could give him is \"Great work in your performance today. Keep up with your perseverance.\""}, {"cid": "a", "text": "Great, you are doing well on this song because of your hard practice. You could do better on other songs and more complex skills if you continue to practice like this."}], "correctChoices": ["a", "b"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}], [{"qid": "Q4", "type": "multiple-choice", "questionText": "Many teachers who have used Jigsaw report that students start to see themselves in a different light -- as more competent, likable, and positive contributors to the classroom. Does the Jigsaw method create a growth-intelligence mindset?", "choices": [{"cid": "d", "text": "Yes, for example carlos, have developed a growth-mindset, while he thought he was stupid he later think he is smart."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "I think so. Because Jigsaw demonstrates to students that they can always learn from other people. What's more, it shows that they can not only learn themselves, but also help other people to improve together."}, {"cid": "a", "text": "Not really, jigsaw does not help students understand the brain or intelligence which is a prerequisite for a growth mindset."}, {"cid": "c", "text": "According to the reading, Carlos changed his mindset because his groupmates think he was someone they could work with and someone they could appreciate."}], "correctChoice": ["a"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}, {"qid": "Q4", "type": "select-all", "questionText": "Many teachers who have used Jigsaw report that students start to see themselves in a different light -- as more competent, likable, and positive contributors to the classroom. Does the Jigsaw method create a growth-intelligence mindset?", "choices": [{"cid": "a", "text": "No, because it doesn\u2019t implicate how the brain works, and the malleable nature of intelligence. Jigsaw doesn't help students or teachers discover why it works, It doesn't help intelligence either."}, {"cid": "c", "text": "Yes, students are encouraged to learn , express, they are seeing others rely on themselves and see themselves improve."}, {"cid": "d", "text": "Yes indeed! The jigsaw method creates a growth mindset because through the process students are going through walks them through a process in which their own competence is demonstrated back to them and they are supported by the other students on their team. This translates to them feeling their own ability to succeed and increase their intelligence in the future."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "Not really, jigsaw does not help students understand the brain or intelligence which is a prerequisite for a growth mindset."}], "correctChoices": ["a", "b"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}, {"qid": "Q4", "type": "multiple-choice", "questionText": "Many teachers who have used Jigsaw report that students start to see themselves in a different light -- as more competent, likable, and positive contributors to the classroom. Does the Jigsaw method create a growth-intelligence mindset?", "choices": [{"cid": "c", "text": "Yes indeed! The jigsaw method creates a growth mindset because through the process students are going through walks them through a process in which their own competence is demonstrated back to them and they are supported by the other students on their team. This translates to them feeling their own ability to succeed and increase their intelligence in the future."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "Yes, students are encouraged to learn , express, they are seeing others rely on themselves and see themselves improve."}, {"cid": "d", "text": "Yes, because it gives them the confidence that they can master a concept enough to teach others and help others do well when tested on that concept."}, {"cid": "a", "text": "No, because it doesn\u2019t implicate how the brain works, and the malleable nature of intelligence. Jigsaw doesn't help students or teachers discover why it works, It doesn't help intelligence either."}], "correctChoice": ["a"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}, {"qid": "Q4", "type": "select-all", "questionText": "Many teachers who have used Jigsaw report that students start to see themselves in a different light -- as more competent, likable, and positive contributors to the classroom. Does the Jigsaw method create a growth-intelligence mindset?", "choices": [{"cid": "c", "text": "Yes, because it gives them the confidence that they can master a concept enough to teach others and help others do well when tested on that concept."}, {"cid": "b", "text": "I would say no, because growth mindset is an idea that through struggling one can do better and Jigsaw does not really do this. Moreover, students usually misunderstand even why jigsaw works."}, {"cid": "d", "text": "I think so. Because Jigsaw demonstrates to students that they can always learn from other people. What's more, it shows that they can not only learn themselves, but also help other people to improve together."}, {"cid": "a", "text": "No"}], "correctChoices": ["a", "b"], "correctFeedback": "Correct.", "incorrectFeedback": "Incorrect."}]]